Running on R3CT40AJ4EP
 > Flow 050-job-workflow-single-company
Run sub-flows/_go-to-home.yaml...
  Open ${EXPO_URL}... COMPLETED
  Wait for animation to end... COMPLETED
  Wait for animation to end... COMPLETED
  Run ../002-login-flow.yaml when id: connection-screen is visible...
  Run ../002-login-flow.yaml when id: connection-screen is visible... SKIPPED
  Run flow when id: create-job-modal is visible...
  Run flow when id: create-job-modal is visible... SKIPPED
  Run flow when id: calendar-day-screen is visible...
  Run flow when id: calendar-day-screen is visible... SKIPPED
  Run flow when id: calendar-month-screen is visible...
  Run flow when id: calendar-month-screen is visible... SKIPPED
  Run flow when id: home-screen is not visible...
  Run flow when id: home-screen is not visible... SKIPPED
  Run flow when id: home-screen is not visible...
  Run flow when id: home-screen is not visible... SKIPPED
  Run flow when id: home-screen is not visible...
  Run flow when id: home-screen is not visible... SKIPPED
  Run flow when id: home-screen is not visible...
  Run flow when id: home-screen is not visible... SKIPPED
  Run flow when id: home-screen is not visible...
  Run flow when id: home-screen is not visible... SKIPPED
  Assert that id: home-calendar-btn is visible... COMPLETED
Run sub-flows/_go-to-home.yaml... COMPLETED
Tap on id: home-calendar-btn... COMPLETED
Assert that id: calendar-month-screen is visible... COMPLETED
Tap on id: calendar-month-day-25... COMPLETED
Assert that id: calendar-day-screen is visible... COMPLETED
Tap on id: calendar-day-create-job-fab... COMPLETED
Assert that id: create-job-modal is visible... COMPLETED
Tap on id: create-job-client-search... COMPLETED
Input text E2E... COMPLETED
Hide Keyboard... COMPLETED
Assert that "E2E Client" is visible... COMPLETED
Tap on "E2E Client"... COMPLETED
